<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chisinau</string>
    <string name="string">string</string>
    <string name="airport">Airport</string>
    <string name="airport_description">Moldova\'s main international airport, located 13 km (8.1 mi) southeast of the centre of Chisinau. It serves as headquarters for Air Moldova, the country\'s national airline. Chisinau International Airport offers connections to major destinations, within Europe and Asia. Address: Aeroportului 80/30 Str, Chisinau MD 2026 Tel: +373 22 525 111</string>
    <string name="zaxi_description">Zaxi brings a sophisticated and elegant experience of fine dining to Chisinau. This upscale restaurant offers a contemporary presentation of the Asian Fusion dining style, respecting the traditions of these diverse food cultures. With a special note comes the Asian Fusion cuisine created by our Award-winning International and Asian chefs. The panoramic views of the city and live music on Tuesdays and Fridays make the dining experience unforgettable. Address: Address: str. Mitropolit Varlaam 77, Chisinau Moldova. Tel: +373 78 201 210.</string>
    <string name="popasul_dacilor_decription">A luxurious rustic restaurant with delicious traditional moldavian food. The restaurant is famous for its remarkable atmosphere, carefully selected dishes and outstanding wines. Address: str. Valea Crucii, 13, Chisinau, Moldova. Tel: +373 691 50 543.</string>
    <string name="roata_vremii_description">A rustic moldavian restaurant with traditional food and quality wine. Address: Hristo Botev, 8, Chisinau 2043 Tel: 37322664489</string>
    <string name="food_and_drink">Food and Drink</string>
    <string name="leogrand_hotel_description">Located in Chisinau city center, the Radisson Blu Leogrand Hotel is within walking distance of Sky Tower Business Center. Many embassies and businesses are only a few minutes away. You can visit attractions such as Nativity Cathedral and Stefan Cel Mare Park, and arrange a winery tour with the help of our concierge desk. We offer transfer service to and from Chisinau International Airport, just 15 kilometers from the hotel. Address: str. Mitropolit Varlaam 77, Chisinau Moldova, Republic of. Tel: 373 (22) 201201</string>
    <string name="nobil_hotel_description">Nobil Luxury Boutique Hotel Moldova is a splendid five star Chisinau hotel, with 34 rooms, including Ambassador and Presidential Suites, the best dining in Chisinau - a gorgeous panoramic restaurant unique in Moldova , with amazing city views and a rooftop terrace, an English Cigars Club, a Conference Hall, an exclusive SPA Center, a Fitness Center, and a wonderful DESSANGE™ Beauty Salon. Address: 49/1, M. Eminescu Street, MD 2012, Chisinau, Moldova Tel: (+373 22) 400 400.</string>
    <string name="alon_hotel_description">Jolly Alon Hotel welcomes guests in the center of Chisinau meters away from theaters, the cathedral and the parliament building. The hotel opened its doors in 1970 and was remodeled in 2000. The great location of Jolly Alon Hotel provides an easy access to Stefan The Great City Park, Parcul Alunelul and National Museum of Archeology and History of Moldova within a 5-minute walk. This elegant venue is situated 450 meters away from Birth of Christ Cathedral, Cathedral Park and The Triumphal Arch Chisinau.There are 80 guestrooms featuring Executive Three Room Suite, Spacious Suite and Deluxe Single Room equipped with a seating area, free Wi-Fi, individual climate control, a minibar and a work area. Many guestrooms offer views of Cathedral Park. They also comprise en suite bathrooms appointed with toiletries, a hairdryer and bathrobes. Address: 37, M. Cibotari Street, Chisinau, Moldova. Tel: +373 022 881 761</string>
    <string name="hotel">Hotel</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="history_museum_description">The Museum consists of temporary and permanent exhibitions that put on display archaeological objects, a vast collection of arms and armour, a numismatic collection, a photography collection, historical exhibits and military equipment and weapons. Address: 31 August 1989 Str, 121 A, Chisinau MD 2012 Tel: +373 22 24-04-26</string>
    <string name="art_museum_description">National Art Museum of Moldova is situated in the centre of Chisinau and is the only institution of such a type in Republic of Moldova. It is placed in three representative buildings which are genuine architectural monuments erected at the end of the 19th commence of the 20th centuries. At present the funds of National Art Museum of Moldova count more than 39 000 art works and reflects the evolution of arts in the 15th-21st centuries. Address: 31 August 1989 Street, Chisinau, Moldova Tel: +373 022 24 13 03</string>
    <string name="ethnography_museum_description">The National Museum of Ethnography and Natural History is the oldest museum in Moldova known for its rich collections of geological, paleontological, zoological, entomological, archaeological, ethnographic, and numismatic. The museum has more than 135,000 pieces, including important exhibits about the natural history of Moldova. Address: 82 M.Kogilniceanu str., Chisinau Tel: +373 22 244 002</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="purcari_winery_description">Purcari Winery situated 75km from Chisinau city centre is known to the whole world for its premium wines, which have received awards and praise from international competitions like Decanter, Challenge International du Vin, Concours Mondial de Bruxelles, International Wine and Spirit Competition as well as the legendary patronage of the royal court of Great Britain. Address: Purcari, Ștefan-Vodă  Tel:(+373) 24 230 411</string>
    <string name="cricova_winery_description">\"Cricova\" JSC is a pearl of the Moldovan wine that represents an unique underground city well-known all over the world by its huge labyrinths, and especially by its excellent wines. \"Cricova\" is the first winery in Moldova which makes sparkling wine as it was prepared by the monk - wine maker Pierre Perignon. The technology \"Méthode Traditionnelle\" is a complex and thin process, consisting in secondary, in-bottle fermentation and the subconsequent maturation \"cuvée \" Address: Cricova, str. Petru Ungureanu, 1 Tel: +373 22 604 027</string>
    <string name="milestii_winery_description">Surrounded by a romantic aura, that natural wine depository – the biggest in the world – has appeared in the limestone galleries at the depth of 30-85 meters in the 70’s of the previous century.The wines that are stored here are the products of the harvest of different years, between 1986 and 1991. Spirit of the past times is felt in this underground wine city growing out of the large tunnels. Natural limestone galleries with total length of 200 km may be passed by transport. And the streets of the underground wine city, placed on a surface of 55 km, are full of oak buts that are standing there as guardians on the watch . Address: Milestii Mici Village, Ialoveni District, Republic of Moldova, MD-6819. Tel: +373 22 382 333</string>
    <string name="wine_tour">Wine Tour</string>
    <string name="chisinau_airport">Chisinau Airport</string>
    <string name="zaxi_restaurant">Zaxi Restaurant</string>
    <string name="popasul_restaurant">Poapasul Dacilor Restaurant</string>
    <string name="roata__vremii_restaurant">Roata Vremii Restaurant</string>
    <string name="leogrand_hotel">Leogrand Hotel</string>
    <string name="nobil_hotel">Nobil Luxury Boutique Hotel</string>
    <string name="joly_allon_hotel">Joly Allon Hotel</string>
    <string name="google_maps_chisinau_location">https://www.google.co.uk/maps/place/Chisinau,+Moldova/@46.743745,28.5562268,8.25z/data=!4m5!3m4!1s0x40c97c3628b769a1:0x37d1d6305749dd3c!8m2!3d47.0104529!4d28.8638103</string>
    <string name="history_museum_chisinau">The National Museum of History of Moldova</string>
    <string name="fine_arts_museum_chisinau">National Museum of Fine Arts</string>
    <string name="ethnography_museum_chisinau"><![CDATA[The National Museum of Ethnography & Natural History]]></string>
    <string name="puracari_winery">Purcari Winery</string>
    <string name="cricova_winery">Cricova Winery</string>
    <string name="milestii_mici_winery">Milestii Mici Winery</string>
    <string name="location_main">Location</string>
    <string name="airport_main">Airport</string>
    <string name="hotel_main">Hotel</string>
    <string name="wine_tour_main">Wine Tour</string>
    <string name="food_drink_main">Food and Drink</string>
    <string name="museums_main">Museums</string>
</resources>
